Guide to the Talmage Farlow Documentary Film Collection, 1979-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio and Moving Image Materials, 1980-2006 and undated, (45 boxes)
  - [50 total items] Miscellaneous formats of the finished film including 5 Betacam SP (3 duplication copies, 2 master copies), 5 VHS, and 17 DVD. 3 VHS copies of a DeStefano produced 8 minute excerpt of the film for the show Classic Arts Showcase. 2 VHS copies of featured excerpts from the Tal Farlow/Lenny Breau performances. CD versions of the performance audio including Live at the Public Theatre, The Penthouse Session, and Tal Farlow and Lenny Breau. Misc VHS recordings of various TV programs devoted to Tal Farlow. (Box 43)
  - Finished Film; 1 inch Transfer; 8/11/82 (Box 44)
  - Finished Film; 1 inch Stereo Protection Master; 11/27/86 (Box 44)
  - Finished Film; 1 inch, 2 Track; 11/23/89 (Box 44)
  - Finished Film; 1 inch distribution copy; 10/16/89 (Box 44)
  - Finished Film; 1 inch Type C Protection Master (Box 44)
  - 9 VHS recordings of miscellaneous films and TV programs used for research by DeStefano (Box 44)
  - Finished Film; 16 mm Release Print (2 copies) (Box 45)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F025; miscellaneous film elements (Box 57)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F026; miscellaneous film elements (Box 57)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F027; miscellaneous film elements (Box 57)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F028; miscellaneous film elements (Box 57)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F029; miscellaneous film elements (Box 57)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F030; miscellaneous film elements (Box 58)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F031; miscellaneous film elements (Box 58)
- Paper Files, 1979-2011 and undated, (11 boxes) (Box 58)
  Files maintained by Lorenzo DeStefano on the production, distribution and marketing of the Tal Farlow documentary film and its related audio recordings, as well as subsequent VHS and DVD versions. These include business and personal correspondence, reviews and press clippings, promotional materials, contracts and financial records, and artwork and photographs used in the film and its packaging. There are also various materials on Farlow not specifically related to the film: e.g. candid and press photographs, concert reviews, guitar instructional books and magazines. Original folder titles and original order have been maintained.
  - T.F. - Screenings (Box 46)
    Correspondence and materials related to 1999 film screenings.
  - T.F. - Screenings '99 (Box 46)
  - Miami - 9/2000 (Box 46)
  - U.S. Press "T.F." (Box 46)
  - T.F. Scenario - April, 1980 (Box 46)
  - European Press "T.F." (Box 46)
  - "T.F." Misc. Reviews (Box 46)
  - "T.F." 93/94 (Box 46)
  - [Untitled] Copyright, Trademark, Patent Applications (Box 46)
  - T.F. Hi-Def - '98 (Lee Krugman) (Box 46)
  - T.F. - Misc. Correspondence (Box 46)
  - T.F. Funeral/Memorial and Obits - 9/20/98 (Box 47)
  - T.F. - Tribute Concert and Guitar Workshops '96 (Box 47)
  - T.F. - RM Assoc - '95 (Box 47)
    Correspondence related to European film distribution and Farlow European tour.
  - T.F. New Video Box (Box 47)
    Materials and correspondence regarding the design for the Rhapsody Films VHS release.
  - Rhapsody Films (Box 47)
  - R.M. Assoc. Talmage Farlow, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - TF Sndtrk - J-Curve Records (Box 48)
  - TF Sndtrk '99 - Siam Records (Box 48)
  - TF Sndtrk '99 - Rhino Records (Box 48)
  - TF Sndtrk - Shanachie Entertainment '99 (Box 48)
  - TF Sndtrk - GRP Records (Box 48)
  - TF Sndtrk '99 - Knitting Factory Records (Box 48)
  - TF Sndtrk - J. Dorn - 32 Records (Box 48)
  - Telarc Jazz - T.F. Sndtrk '99 (Box 48)
  - TF / Fantasy - Kaffel (Box 48)
  - TF / Verve - Seidel (Box 48)
  - T.F. Sndtrk - Jardis (Box 48)
  - TF Sndtrk '98 (Box 48)
  - T.F. Sndtrk - 96 (Box 48)
  - Tal / Fret Records (Box 48)
  - T.F. Sndtrk - Mosaic Records - M. Cuscuna (Box 48)
  - "T.F." / Hot Licks (Box 48)
    Correspondence related to use of Farlow footage in "Hot Licks" guitar instructional video.
  - Guitar Player Magazine (Box 48)
  - TF - Lenny Stock Ftg (Box 48)
  - R.M. Associates "T.F." (Box 48)
  - TF Sndtrk - Demo CD Labels (Box 48)
    Materials related to The Penthouse Session and Live at the Public Theatre demo CDs.
  - TF Film Collection- U. of N. Texas (Box 48)
  - TF Matls - Original (Box 49)
    Originals of newspaper and magazine articles, press clippings.
  - TF Continuity (Box 49)
  - TF Dialogue Transcript (Box 49)
  - Jersey Shore Jazz Festival 1989 (Box 49)
    Festival press kit.
  - TCB, Cinema Ventures (Box 49)
    Correspondence regarding distribution of film.
  - TF Copyright (Box 49)
  - TF Film Collection (Box 49)
    Correspondence regarding establishment of Tal Farlow Film Collection.
  - TF DVD - Japan - Zoo Corp (Box 49)
  - TF - DVD Distribution - MVD (Box 49)
  - TF DVD Sales Outreach and PR (Box 49)
  - Guitarchives - C. Meeting Sndtrk (Box 49)
  - TF Music Clearance (Box 49)
  - TF Music Clearance (Cue Sheets) (Box 50)
  - TF Radio (U.S.) (Box 50)
  - TF TV Sales (Box 50)
  - C. Meeting - Reviews 97/98 (Box 50)
    Chance Meeting CD reviews.
  - TF Sndtrk - Cue Sheets/Mat'ls (Box 50)
  - TF Sndtrk CD - Public Theatre Set (Box 50)
  - Just Jazz Guitar (Box 50)
    Issue of Just Jazz Guitar magazine with Farlow articles and transcriptions.
  - Tal Farlow Press (Box 50)
  - TF DVD Reviews (Box 50)
  - Tal Farlow Obituaries (Box 50)
  - Website 2000 - "Talmage Farlow" (Box 50)
  - Tal Farlow CD Reviews (Box 50)
  - The Jazz Style of Tal Farlow - Instructional Book (Box 50)
  - T.F. Originals (Box 50)
  - "T.F." Misc. (Old) Publicity Originals (Box 51)
  - "T.F." Mat'ls - Originals/Photos (Box 51)
  - Tal Tribute May 18, 1991 (Box 51)
  - Misc. "T.F." Letters of Reco (Box 51)
    Letters supporting, praising, and recommending the film.
  - Mary Williams (Box 51)
    Music clearence documents.
  - Prod A-propos/Apropos Prod's (Box 51)
    Registration of production company name.
  - Tal/Lenny Footage (Box 51)
    Correspondence regarding usage of Tal Farlow/Lenny Breau footage.
  - C. Meeting - AFM, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    Chance Meeting CD - American Federation of Musicians royalties documents.
  - C. Meeting - Liner Notes (Box 51)
  - T.F./Chance Meeting (Box 52)
  - Living Proof/Triloka/Tal (Box 52)
    Submission of film to Living Proof record label.
  - T.F. Financial Breakdowns, (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Photo Source (Box 52)
    Photographer's contact information.
  - T.F. Mat'ls (Box 52)
    Biographies, press clippings, screening advertisements.
  - "T.F." Bulletin Board (Box 52)
    Miscellaneous notes, correspondences, and promotional materials.
  - Original Treatment and Proposal (Box 52)
  - "Talmage Farlow" Cue Sheets (Box 52)
  - Filmoption Internationale (Box 52)
    Correspondence and documents regarding international distribution of film.
  - Money Received, (2 folders) (Box 52)
    Financial records, statements, and receipts.
  - New Jersey Network (Box 53)
    Correspondence with New Jersey Network regarding sales and distribution.
  - Originals: Final Budget Estimates 8/18/81 (Box 53)
  - "Talmage Farlow" Proposal (Box 53)
  - NJN Legal (Box 53)
    Legal documents (1981-1993) regarding establishment and dissolution of film distribution through the New Jersey Network.
  - Tal Farlow / NJN File, (3 folders) (Box 53)
    Additional correspondence with the New Jersey Network regarding film distribution.
  - Guitarchives (Box 53)
    Correspondence, contracts, and press materials for Chance Meeting CD.
  - Vestapol Videos (Box 53)
    Correspondence, contracts, and press materials for Legends of Jazz Guitar video.
  - New T.F. Flyer (Box 53)
  - Keys and Codes (Box 54)
    Spriral binder of notes from original production of film (1980).
  - T.F. Cut List (Box 54)
  - Chika - Sogovision (Box 54)
    Correspondence and notes regarding Japanese licensing.
  - T.F. - Jimco Records (Box 54)
    Correspondence regarding licensing of audio material.
  - M. Hyk - T. Farlow Liaison (Box 54)
    European Tour information (1990-91).
  - Ricker - Rhapsody (Box 54)
    Contracts and correspondence regarding distribution by Rhapsody films.
  - T.F. Copies (Box 54)
    Photocopies of various film promotional and press materials.
  - T.F. Copies 2 (Box 54)
  - Music Cue Sheets - Misc. (Box 54)
  - Misc. (Box 54)
  - Mr. and Mrs. W.W. Wirth, (2 folders) (Box 54)
    Correspondence with Lydia and Wally Wirth.
  - Tal Farlow Photographs (Box 55)
  - Tal Farlow Publicity Photos (Box 55)
  - Farlow, DiStefano Photos (Box 55)
  - Django Reinhardt Jazz Festival (Box 55)
  - Concord Jazz Festival 1978 (Box 55)
  - T. F. 35 mm Slides (Tal, Tal/Lenny) (Box 55)
  - Bob Cole Signs Prints (Box 55)
  - Oversized Materials (Box 56)
    Additional Robert Cole Signs photographs, film posters, and photographs of Farlow.